{"question_list":[{"question":{"ID":"4","Question":"Which of the following is <br><u>NOT<\/u><\/b> an event in the ABAP programming language","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"End-of-selection","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:45:15"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"End-of-initialization","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:45:15"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Get","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:45:40"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Set","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:45:40"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:46:17"},{"QuestionId":"4","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-06-24 14:46:17"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"5","Question":"What type of memory is typically used as to save default values for screen fields","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Shared Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:04:32"},{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"ABAP\/4 Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:04:32"},{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"SAP-Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:04:32"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"5","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:04:32"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"6","Question":"Select the valid customer defined message","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"MESSAGE Y123","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:48:17"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"MESSAGE E123(9999).","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:48:17"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"MESSAGE ID 'AT' TYPE 'S' NUMBER 100","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:48:55"},{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"MESSAGE E123 by Fielda Fieldb","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:48:55"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"6","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:49:33"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"7","Question":"What happens when a 1 to many relationship is encountered with an inner join","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:04:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Redundant data is not returned to the resultant set","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:52:59"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Redundant data from the outer table is included","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:52:59"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Run time error","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:54:05"},{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Redundant data from the inner table is included","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:54:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"7","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:54:38"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"8","Question":"What must be assigned to Search Helps","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Data Element","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:56:51"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Domain","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:56:51"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Values","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:57:35"},{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Nothing","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:57:35"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"8","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 14:58:30"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"9","Question":"What is contained in variable SY-LINSZ","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Row count of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 15:04:41"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Height of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 15:04:41"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Width of the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 15:05:45"},{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"No of characters in the current line","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 15:05:45"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"9","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-06-29 15:05:59"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"12","Question":"What determines if a table is client specific or client independent","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"The first field is mandt with a external data type CLNT and specified as a key field","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 14:11:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Depends how Basis has configured the client","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 14:11:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The first field is mandt with a domain CLNT but not specified as a key field","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 14:11:02"},{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The option 'Client Specified' is added to the Select statement","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 14:13:23"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"12","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-06-30 14:11:02"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"14","Question":"Default page headings are created on which list types","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"All Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:07:55"},{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Basic Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:07:55"},{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Secondary Lists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:07:55"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"14","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:07:55"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"15","Question":"Program A issues the following statement: SUBMIT PROGRAM B.\n<br>\nSelect the correct statement","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Program A becomes active in the same internal session of Program B","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:11:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Program B becomes active in the same internal session of Program A","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:11:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"User Context is flushed","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:11:41"},{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Program B runs in a new internal session","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:11:41"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"15","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:11:41"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"16","Question":"If there are no entries in <b>itab<\/b> then what is the result of the following select:\n<br>\n<b>Select * from DBTAB for all entries in itab where key1 = itab-key1.<\/b>","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Run time error","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:15:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"All entries from DBTAB are retrieved","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:15:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Only distinct values for key1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:15:59"},{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"No entries are retrieved","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:15:59"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"16","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:15:59"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"18","Question":"What is needed to ensure that a check field is verified against the referenced key field of the check table","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"same data type only is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:21:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"all key fields MUST have domain equality between check table and foreign key table","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:21:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"same domain is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:21:35"},{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"same data element is required for check field and referenced field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:21:35"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"18","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:21:35"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"19","Question":"What is an example of Organizational Data","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Sales Order","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:22:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Country Keys","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:22:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Cost Centres","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:22:56"},{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Vendors","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:22:56"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"19","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:22:56"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"20","Question":"What are the valid attributes of a domain","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Label","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Length","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Fixed Values","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Type","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"},{"QuestionId":"20","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:24:05"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"21","Question":"What are the main functions of Data Dictionary","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"To insulate the developer from the database","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"To provide data security at the application level","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"To connect to the operating system","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"To support the creation and management of metadata","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"},{"QuestionId":"21","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:30:09"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"22","Question":"Programs that extend beyond transactional limits and want to pass data should use:","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"SAP Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:32:21"},{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Tables","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:32:21"},{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"ABAP\/4 memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:32:21"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"22","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:32:21"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"23","Question":"Which of the following is an invalid method of populating an internal table","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Insert ITAB","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Append","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Read Table ITAB","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Select * into Table ITAB from dbtab.","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"},{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"Collect","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"23","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:34:13"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"24","Question":"Identify the clause that is used to suppress standard headers","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"No Standard Heading","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:35:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"No Standard Page Heading","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:35:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Suppress Standard","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:35:22"},{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"System>List>Save","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:35:22"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"24","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-02 14:35:22"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"25","Question":"You have made changes to an existing table that contains data. What takes place when the Database Conversion utility is executed ?","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:04:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Data in the table is automatically deleted and must be reloaded","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The table in the database is renamed and eventually deleted","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The indexes for the table needs to manually be reconstructed in the ABAP Dictionary","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The revised table in the ABAP\/4 Dictionary is activated","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"The table in the database is recreated","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"},{"QuestionId":"25","OptionId":"5","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:00:42"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"26","Question":"After a READ LINE on a list, what happens to the HIDE data","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"26","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Nothing, the data remains in the hidden area","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:07:18"},{"QuestionId":"26","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The hide data isrestored to shared memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:07:18"},{"QuestionId":"26","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The Hide data is not available to the program","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:07:18"},{"QuestionId":"26","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"It is transferred back to the fields defined in the program","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:07:18"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"26","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:07:18"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"27","Question":"Where does information come from when you press F1 on a screen field","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"27","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Data element documentation","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:13:25"},{"QuestionId":"27","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Domain short text","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:13:25"},{"QuestionId":"27","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Search help","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:13:25"},{"QuestionId":"27","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Domain Help values","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:13:25"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"27","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:13:25"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"28","Question":"What will cause the AT USER-COMMAND to fire.","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"28","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Type S Function Codes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:15:05"},{"QuestionId":"28","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Type T Functions Codes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:15:05"},{"QuestionId":"28","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Normal Function Codes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:15:05"},{"QuestionId":"28","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Function Codes that Start with P","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:15:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"28","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:15:05"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"29","Question":"What are the coordinates of the following Modal Dialog Box.\nWindow Starting at 10 20\nEnding at 20 30","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"29","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Starting at Column 10, Row 20 Ending at Column 20, Row 30","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:17:05"},{"QuestionId":"29","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Starting at Column 10, Row 30 Ending at Column 20, Row 20","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:17:05"},{"QuestionId":"29","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Starting at Row 10, Column 20 Ending at Row 20, Column 30","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:17:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"29","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:17:05"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"30","Question":"What is the effect of the Collect Statement if an entry with the same key already exists","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:45:13","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"30","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Appends a new line","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:21:11"},{"QuestionId":"30","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"adds the numeric fields to an existing entry","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:21:11"},{"QuestionId":"30","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Creates a new entry","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:21:11"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"30","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:21:11"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"31","Question":"How are buffers used by inner and outer joins","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:04:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"31","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Buffers are always used","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:23:07"},{"QuestionId":"31","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Buffers are always bypassed","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:23:07"},{"QuestionId":"31","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The choice can be made to use or bypass buffers","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:23:07"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"31","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:23:07"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"32","Question":"Mark the code that will display the selection screen of the called program ZTST.","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"32","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"SUBMIT ZTST VIA SELECTION-SCREEN","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:25:28"},{"QuestionId":"32","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"SUBMIT ZTST AND RETURN","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:25:28"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"32","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:25:28"},{"QuestionId":"32","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:25:28"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"34","Question":"What requirement exists if a field is defined in the dictionary of type CURR","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"34","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Decimals must be defined in the domain","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:30:58"},{"QuestionId":"34","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The field must be numeric","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:30:58"},{"QuestionId":"34","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The field must be linked to another field of type CUKY","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:30:58"},{"QuestionId":"34","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"No other requirement exists","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:30:58"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"34","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:30:58"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"35","Question":"Identify the case where the table buffering should be set off","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"35","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"For Global Master Data","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:34:49"},{"QuestionId":"35","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"When the most current data is not required","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:34:49"},{"QuestionId":"35","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"When the most current data is required","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:34:49"},{"QuestionId":"35","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"For Small Static non volatile tables","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:34:49"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"35","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 04:34:49"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"37","Question":"What is true about views","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:15","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"A view contains data","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"},{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Maintenance Views are not updateable","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"},{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"A view is aurtomatically created on the database upon activation","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"},{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Views can be buffered","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"},{"QuestionId":"37","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-05 05:06:28"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"45","Question":"A screen field is dynamically changed in a dialog program.\n<br>\nWhen does it get re-initialized ?","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"45","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"At the end of the transaction","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:18:46"},{"QuestionId":"45","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Only when the program encounters more code to modify the field attributes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:18:46"},{"QuestionId":"45","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"At PAI execution","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:18:46"},{"QuestionId":"45","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"At PBO execution","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:18:46"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"45","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:18:46"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"46","Question":"What is true about <b>LEAVE TO LIST-PROCESSING<\/b> event","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:27:22","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Enables execution of interactive reporting events","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"},{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Data available in the dialog program must be passed to the list","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"},{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Enables processing of ok_code functions","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"},{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The invoking module pool still retains control of execution","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"},{"QuestionId":"46","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:35:13"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"47","Question":"What is true about using memory to pass data","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"ABAP memory is local to each external session","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Each external session has its own ABAP memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"SAP Memory can be accessed by all external sessions","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"ABAP memory can be accessed by SAP memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"ABAP memory is used to pass data between the external sessions of an internal session","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"},{"QuestionId":"47","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:45:57"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"49","Question":"How do you reset the context of your program","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Issue a COMMIT WORK statement","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"},{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Issue a ROLLBACK WORK statement in the program","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"},{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"End the dialog program","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"},{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Issue a termination message (type A)","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"},{"QuestionId":"49","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:48:44"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"50","Question":"What type of memory is retained for the duration of external session","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"50","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Extended Memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:49:45"},{"QuestionId":"50","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"SAP memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:49:45"},{"QuestionId":"50","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"ABAP\/4 memory","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:49:45"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"50","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:49:45"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"52","Question":"What steps would be required to define a Tabstrip in your dialog program","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Declare a Tabstrip control in your global top include","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"},{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Name your tabstrip object","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"},{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Define Pushbuttons on the subscreen area","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"},{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Place a tabstrip object on your screen using Screen Painter","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"},{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"},{"QuestionId":"52","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-11 14:54:08"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"53","Question":"Which is not an automatic check carried out the by screen processor","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"format Check","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"},{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Obligatory Field Check","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"},{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Fixed Values","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"},{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Foreign Key Check","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"},{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"Parameter Id Validation","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"53","OptionId":"5","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:45:39"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"54","Question":"Why is it a good idea to use back up version of the OK_CODE","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"54","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"OK_CODE is a system reserved variable and cannot be accessed directly","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:46:50"},{"QuestionId":"54","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Because the OK_CODE gets reset at the beginning","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:46:50"},{"QuestionId":"54","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"To prevent accidental setting of the OK_CODE in a different screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:46:50"},{"QuestionId":"54","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"So the OK_CODE is freed up for subscreens","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:46:50"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"54","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-12 13:46:50"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"55","Question":"Why should one choose to use Asynchronous DB updates in ABAP Program","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:51:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Immediate updates to the Database are required","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"},{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"your updates need to run together as a logical unit","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"},{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"To improve user response time","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"},{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"your program need the updates completed in order to continue processing","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"},{"QuestionId":"55","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:50:30"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"60","Question":"Using Screen painter how do you logically relate the radio buttons","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"60","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Ensure the prefix name of the radio buttons is the same","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:47:18"},{"QuestionId":"60","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Encompass them in a Radio Button Group","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:47:18"},{"QuestionId":"60","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Define a Group box","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:47:18"},{"QuestionId":"60","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Make sure each one has the same Screen Group Name","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:47:18"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"60","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:47:18"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"62","Question":"Where should the CANCEL (Red x) button on the standard tool bar take the user ?","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"62","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"To where the transaction was called","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:56:43"},{"QuestionId":"62","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"To the initial screen of the transaction","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:56:43"},{"QuestionId":"62","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"To the previous screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:56:43"},{"QuestionId":"62","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"To the cancel area","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:56:43"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"62","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 03:56:43"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"63","Question":"What message type <b>does not<\/b> implicitly trigger database commits for the table updates specified in your program.","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:04:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"I type MESSAGE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"},{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"A type MESSAGE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"},{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"E type MESSAGE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"},{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"W type MESSAGE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"},{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"S type MESSAGE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"63","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:11:59"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"64","Question":"What methods could be used to specify the next screen to be displayed","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Set Screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"},{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Use the Next Screen Option on the Screen Attributes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"},{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Loop at Screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"},{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Submit Screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"},{"QuestionId":"64","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:20:47"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"65","Question":"What is true about dialog programs","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"The flow logic is contained in Modules","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"},{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Dialog Programs do not require a transaction to execute the module pool","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"},{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Screens are optional in a dialog program","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"},{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Transactions are a vehicle to execute dialog programs","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"},{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"update and enqueue techniques are important","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"},{"QuestionId":"65","OptionId":"5","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:24:00"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"66","Question":"What is the use of OK_CODE","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"66","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"contains screen field values","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:25:24"},{"QuestionId":"66","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"contains function codes","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:25:24"},{"QuestionId":"66","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"determines successful user action","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:25:24"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"66","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:25:24"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"67","Question":"What is true about subscreens","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Multiple subscreens are possible in a single screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"},{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"You can also specify the subscreens dynamically at runtime","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"},{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Can set their own titlebar","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"},{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Can set their own GUI status","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"},{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"5","OptionValue":"have their own OK_CODE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"},{"QuestionId":"67","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-13 04:28:27"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"68","Question":"After a user event is performed, which event is  triggered in Dialog Program","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"68","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Case OK_CODE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:30:56"},{"QuestionId":"68","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"PAI","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:30:56"},{"QuestionId":"68","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Module User_command","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:30:56"},{"QuestionId":"68","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"PBO","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:30:56"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"68","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:30:56"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"70","Question":"The following statement <b>MESSAGE S001(AT)<\/b> is issued in a PAI module of a dynpro.\n<br> \nWhere does the message appear ?","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"70","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"On the same screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:36:01"},{"QuestionId":"70","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"On the next screen","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:36:01"},{"QuestionId":"70","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"After the AT-EXIT Module","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:36:01"},{"QuestionId":"70","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"In the System Log","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:36:01"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"70","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-14 13:36:01"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"73","Question":"When would you use one of the F4_IF* functions ","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"73","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"In the module that perform OKCODE processing","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:33:58"},{"QuestionId":"73","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"In the PAI when Process on Value-Request dialog event is triggered","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:33:58"},{"QuestionId":"73","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"In the PBO when Process on Value-Request dialog event is triggered","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:33:58"},{"QuestionId":"73","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"In the PAI when Process on Help-Request dialog event is tgriggered","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:33:58"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"73","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:33:58"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"74","Question":"What is the difference between call screen and set screen","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"74","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"There is no difference","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:35:10"},{"QuestionId":"74","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Call Screen is used only for external screens. Set screen is only for screens in the same module pool","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:35:10"},{"QuestionId":"74","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Call screen executes and returns to the point of call. Set Screen does not","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:35:10"},{"QuestionId":"74","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Set screen executes and returns to the point of call. Call Screen does not","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:35:10"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"74","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:35:10"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"75","Question":"Indicate the functions that are capable of transporting data to the screen fields","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"DYNP_VALUES_UPDATE","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"},{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"DYNP_VALUES_READ","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"},{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"DYNPREAD","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"},{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"F4IF_FIELD_VALUE_REQUEST","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"},{"QuestionId":"75","OptionId":"4","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:36:35"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"79","Question":"What statement in a dialog programming makes screen fields available for input","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"79","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Field","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:46:04"},{"QuestionId":"79","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Module","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:46:04"},{"QuestionId":"79","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Check","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:46:04"},{"QuestionId":"79","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Case","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:46:04"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"79","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:46:04"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"80","Question":"What is the proper coding practice in the flow logic of a Dynpro when a subscreen is defined on the screen","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"80","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Call Subscreen in the PAI and PBO","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:47:50"},{"QuestionId":"80","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"The Call Subscreen statement is not required","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:47:50"},{"QuestionId":"80","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Call Subscreen in the PAI only","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:47:50"},{"QuestionId":"80","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Call Subscreen in the PBO only","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:47:50"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"80","OptionId":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:47:50"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"82","Question":"What happens after each dialog step","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:04:38","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"82","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"A Commit Work is executed","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:50:39"},{"QuestionId":"82","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"System does a implicit commit","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:50:39"},{"QuestionId":"82","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"The application gathers data for update processing","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:50:39"},{"QuestionId":"82","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"The SAP LUW is concluded","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:50:39"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"82","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:50:39"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"84","Question":"Where is the modification group assignment of fields defined","Level":"1","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:17:52","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"84","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"In the screen painter","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:54:02"},{"QuestionId":"84","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"In the Dynpro","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:54:02"},{"QuestionId":"84","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Using the SET GROUP statement","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:54:02"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"84","OptionId":"3","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 13:54:02"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"86","Question":"<b>CALL FUNCTION STARTING NEW TASK<\/b> is an example of what type of of call","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:55:36","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"86","OptionId":"4","OptionValue":"Direct","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:53:05"},{"QuestionId":"86","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Synchronous","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:53:05"},{"QuestionId":"86","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Asynchronous","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:53:05"},{"QuestionId":"86","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Batch","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:53:05"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"86","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:53:05"}],"meta":[]},{"question":{"ID":"92","Question":"You have issued a SET TITLEBAR in PBO of your screen.\n<br>\nHow long will the title bar remain active","Level":"2","ChoiceType":"1","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:33","ActiveStatus":"X"},"options":[{"QuestionId":"92","OptionId":"1","OptionValue":"Until the Next screen change","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:04:45"},{"QuestionId":"92","OptionId":"2","OptionValue":"Until the next Set TitleBar statement","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:04:45"},{"QuestionId":"92","OptionId":"3","OptionValue":"Until the next DB Luw","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:04:45"}],"answers":[{"QuestionId":"92","OptionId":"2","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:04:45"}],"meta":[]}],"quiz_list":[{"quiz":{"QuizId":"3","Description":"ABAP Basics - 1","Count":"10","Level":"1","QuestionIds":"4,5,6,14,15,16,23,24,28,30","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:44:26","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"3","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-08 14:45:41"},{"QuizId":"3","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 15:01:31"}]},{"quiz":{"QuizId":"4","Description":"ABAP Concepts - 1","Count":"10","Level":"2","QuestionIds":"9,22,26,32,46,47,49,50,55,86","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 14:55:41","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"4","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-08 14:45:41"},{"QuizId":"4","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-09 15:01:31"}]},{"quiz":{"QuizId":"6","Description":"DB Concepts - 1","Count":"5","Level":"2","QuestionIds":"7,25,31,63,82","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:03:30","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"6","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:05:46"},{"QuizId":"6","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:05:46"}]},{"quiz":{"QuizId":"8","Description":"DDIC Basics - 1","Count":"10","Level":"1","QuestionIds":"8,12,18,19,20,21,27,34,35,37","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:36","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"8","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:58"},{"QuizId":"8","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:11:58"}]},{"quiz":{"QuizId":"9","Description":"Module Pool Basics - 1","Count":"10","Level":"1","QuestionIds":"29,45,53,54,60,64,66,68,80,84","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:18:06","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"9","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:15:05"},{"QuizId":"9","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:15:05"}]},{"quiz":{"QuizId":"10","Description":"Module Pool Concepts - 1","Count":"10","Level":"2","QuestionIds":"52,62,65,67,70,73,74,75,79,92","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:19:18","ActiveStatus":"X"},"meta":[{"QuizId":"10","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Premium","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:15:22"},{"QuizId":"10","MetaKey":"sync","MetaValue":"Free","CreatedAt":"2013-07-16 15:15:22"}]}]}
